

### **CONTACT ME AT**

dbhairi@gmail.com

+91-9209562971, 8668328408

in @dattatrybhairi

Bangalore, India

# PERSONAL INFO

• D.O.B: 28-July-1995

## SKILLS SUMMARY

••• Project Management

•••• Software Development

•••• Hardware Development

••• Operating Systems & Services

#### AWARDS RECEIVED

Best Outgoing Student of The College - Year 2017 (NBNSCOE).

5 Times Successive Winner
Project Competition outside
the college.

Winner in "Photography" at inter-college Competition

## **HOBBIES & INTEREST**

Photography

Listening to Music

▶ Watching Tech stuff on Web

്റ Riding Bike

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

- English (R,W,S)
- Hindi (R,W,S)
- Marathi (R,W,S)
- Telugu (S)
- Kannada(S)

# DATTATRAY BHAIRI

# EMBEDDED SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

Around 3 Years of Experience in design, development & testing of real-time embedded applications using C, C++, Python & embedded development tools & cloud based Client & Server Appln. Good understanding of embedded Hardware & Software design to support IoT Appln.

#### CORE COMPETENCIES

Embedded C, Python, RTOS, ROS, IoT Concepts, Linux,IAR, CCS, Keil, 8051, RF Devices, LORA-WAN, mmWave, GIT,SLAM, ZigBee, MQTT,Raspberry Pi, Arduino, Intel Boards, TI's CC25xx, CC26XX Soc, ESPWROOM32, ESP8266, BLE, & other protocols and PIC Controllers.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Embedded Software Engineer**

Vacus Tech Pvt. Ltd. Banglore. | Jul 2019 - present

- Working on Social Distancing Tags, Contact Tracing Projects.
- Working on Intel UP and UP Squared Boards.
- Written Firmware for CC26XX/CC26XX SOC's, and Tested using IAR & CCS embedded tool.
- Design and Development of RF network using ISM and Sub-gig Bands, BLE.
- Worked on Design of Various types of Antennas.
- Worked on project Di-fence (Digital Fence).
- Responsible for the maintenance and support of any new software features that are deployed into the Di-fence system.
- Design and Development of IoT Platform Devices.

# **Embedded Engineer**

Akruti Technologies. Pune | Nov 2017 - Dec 2018

- Worked on Embedded based Projects(8051 ASM, C, PIC, ATmega).
- Built low power IoT projects for industry support. ( Wireless Data acquisition ).
- Worked on Various Designs and Testing Responses of AC Power Supply.
- Designed and Developed Transformer-less Power Supply for low Power IoT devices.

# **Embedded Engineer (Trainee)**

CircuitBaord.in, Solapur | Feb 2015 - May 2017

 Worked on DIY (Do-it-Yourself) projects, & used to conduct workshops on the same topics for College Students under "CircuitBoard" by providing certificates and internships.

#### **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

# Solapur University

Bechelor of Engineering In ECE | Jun 2014 - Jun 2017

Percentage: 66.52%

## State Technical Board

Diploma In ECE | Jun 2012 - May 2014

• Percentage: 69.03%